A Guide to the Williams Family Papers, 1819-1993
Thomas Balch Library
- (Box Williams Family)
  - Harrison Williams, cancelled checks, 1909
  - Harrison Williams, Sons of the Revolution membership certificate, 1909
  - Harrison Williams, cancelled checks, 1910
  - Harrison Williams, receipts, 1910, 1937, 1944
  - Harrison Williams, cancelled checks, 1911
  - Harrison Williams, stamped envelope, 10 April 1911
  - Harrison Williams, Veteran Corps of Artillery, S.N.Y. certificate, 15 November 1911
  - Harrison Williams, cancelled checks, 1912
  - Harrison Williams, The Human Factor v.2 no. 5, 26 July 1915
  - Harrison Williams, House of Representatives pass, 6 January 1920
  - Harrison Williams, University of Virginia Journal of Engineering, May 1925
  - Harrison Williams, Catalogue of the Episcopal High School in Virginia Near Alexandria, 1925-1926
  - Harrison Williams, Cleveland Terminals Building Company prospectus, 24 November 1926
  - Harrison Williams, clippings, 1926-1935, n.d.
  - Harrison Williams, will, January 1929
  - Harrison Williams, Roxbury Hall, 1935-1937
  - Harrison Williams, Loudoun County church history, 1936
  - Harrison Williams, C.G. Sloan & Col., Inc. auction catalogues, 1941
  - Harrison Williams, World War II propaganda, ca. 1941
  - Harrison Williams, War Savings Bond applications, ca. 1942
  - Harrison Williams, 4th War Bond Drive flyer, 1943
  - Harrison Williams, Virginia War History Project, 1943, 1945
  - Harrison Williams, Virginia in Wartime 1942-1943, 1944
  - Harrison Williams, "Vision After Victory" sermon, 8 May 1945
  - Harrison Williams, The Association Against the Prohibition Amendment, Inc. membership card, n.d.
  - Harrison Williams, bookplates, n.d.
  - Harrison & Jane Abbott Williams, wedding place cards, 8 May 1901
  - Harrison & Jane Abbott Williams, correspondence, 1904
  - Jane Abbott Williams, correspondence, 1903, 6-8 February 1904
  - Jane Abbott Williams, correspondence, 9-20 February 1904, n.d.
- (Box Williams Family)
  - Harrison & Pauline Winslow Williams, correspondence, 1910-1913, 1917-1918
  - Harrison & Pauline Winslow Williams, correspondence, January-April 1919
  - Harrison & Pauline Winslow Williams, correspondence, June-December 1919, 1920
  - Harrison & Pauline Winslow Williams, correspondence, 1929-1930
  - Harrison & Pauline Winslow Williams, cards, 1915, 1918, n.d.
  - Harrison & Pauline Winslow Williams, Company B 49th US Infantry Christmas menu, 1917
  - Harrison & Pauline Winslow Williams, envelopes from Gordon Williams, 1918-1919
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, correspondence, 1910-1914
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, correspondence, 1915, 1917-1918
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, correspondence, 1927-1928
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, correspondence, September-October 1929
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, correspondence, November 1929
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, correspondence, December 1929
- (Box Williams Family)
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, correspondence, January-March 1930
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, correspondence, April 1930
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, correspondence, 1-13 May 1930
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, correspondence, 14 May-July 1930, 1932
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, checks #585-592, 1924
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, checks #610-699, 1925-1926
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, checks #700-800, 1926-1927
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, checks #801-900, 1927-1928
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, checks #901-1000, 1928-1929
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, checks #1001-1100, 1929
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, checks #1101-1141, 1929-1930
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, poem "The Winslow Vault", 30 September 1855
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, confirmation card, 22 April 1888
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, clippings, 1901-1928, n.d.
- (Box Williams Family)
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, Henry C. Winslow wedding invitation, 26 August 1903
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, Union Telegraph Company frank, 1904
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, wedding gift list, 29 December 1910
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, wedding memorabilia, December 1910
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, miscellaneous, 1910, 1931, n.d.
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, receipts, 1910-1911
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, stamped envelope, 14 March 1911
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, anniversary memorabilia, 29 December 1911
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, gift tags, 1913
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, calling cards, 1913, n.d.
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, bank book, 1915-1927
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, accounts, 1925-1933, n.d.
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, stock purchases, 1927-1929
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, bank statements, 1927-1930
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, receipts, 1928
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, receipts, 1929-1930
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, savings account, 1929-1933
  - Pauline Winslow Williams, bank book, 1929
  - Pauline Winslow Williams Estate, transfer of securities, December 1933
  - Pauline Winslow Williams Estate, transfer of securities, January 1934
  - Pauline Winslow Williams Estate, transfer of securities, February 1934
  - Pauline Winslow Williams Estate, transfer of securities, March-December 1934
  - Pauline Winslow Williams Estate, legal documents, 1930-1934
  - Pauline Winslow Williams Estate, legal documents, 1935-1944
  - Pauline Winslow Williams Estate, Cleveland property correspondence, January-March 1934
  - Pauline Winslow Williams Estate, Cleveland property correspondence, April-May 1934
  - Pauline Winslow Williams Estate, Cleveland property correspondence, June 1934
- (Box Williams Family)
  - Pauline Winslow Williams Estate, Cleveland property correspondence, July-December 1934
  - Pauline Winslow Williams Estate, Cleveland property correspondence, January-April 1935
  - Pauline Winslow Williams Estate, Cleveland property correspondence, May-June 1935
  - Pauline Winslow Williams Estate, Cleveland property legal documents, 1907, 1911
  - Pauline Winslow Williams Estate, Cleveland property legal documents, 1934-1935
  - Harrison & Joan Stafford-Allen Williams, S.S. Penland passenger list, 18 September 1937
  - Joan Stafford-Allen Williams, correspondence, 1946
  - Harrison Williams Jr., correspondence, 1904-1919, n.d.
  - Harrison Williams Jr., obituary, 1928
  - Harrison Williams Jr., bookplates, n.d.
  - Harrison Williams Jr. & Winslow Williams, postcards, 25 January 1919
  - Winslow Williams, correspondence, 1913-1930, n.d.
  - Winslow Williams, correspondence, 1933-1934, 1937
  - Winslow Williams, correspondence, 1968-1993
  - Winslow Williams, financial records, 1943-1946
  - Winslow Williams, baptismal certificate, 27 November 1913
  - Winslow Williams, debarkation card, 1936
  - Winslow Williams, marriage certificate, 6 February 1937
  - Winslow Williams, account books, 1944-1945
- (Box Williams Family, Winslow Family)
  - Winslow Williams, articles and clippings, 1953-1990
  - Winslow Williams, Nathan Winslow Estate papers, September 1975
  - Winslow Williams, obituary, 1993
  - Winslow Williams, draft will, n.d
  - Winslow Williams, miscellaneous, n.d
  - Winslow & Helen Constance Moore Williams, wedding telegrams, 1936-1937
  - Winslow & Helen Constance Moore Williams, ship's menu, 12 February 1937
  - Winslow & Helen Constance Moore Williams, ship's passenger list, 6 March 1937
  - Winslow & Helen Constance Moore Williams, postcards of Santiago de Chile, ca. 1937
  - Winslow & Helen Constance Moore Williams, booklet "Golden Hours Along the Spanish Main", ca. 1937
  - Helen Constance Moore Williams, clippings, 1937
  - Helen Constance Moore Williams, birthday card, October 1955
  - Helen Constance Moore Williams, obituary, September 1991
  - Helen Constance Moore Williams, memorial program, 12 September 1991
  - Williams Family, Arthur Hale Abbott memorial, 1915
  - Williams Family, calling cards, n.d.
  - Williams Family, Metropolitan Fair Fourth Private Concert program, n.d.
  - Nathan Winslow, will, 1880
  - Mary A. Winslow, will, 1885
  - Richard Winslow Estate, legal documents, 1901-1916
  - Richard Winslow Estate, legal documents, 1934-1937
  - William G. Winslow Estate, correspondence, 1903-1911
  - William G. Winslow Estate, legal documents, 1910-1911
  - William G. Winslow Estate, receipts, 1911-1912
  - William G. Winslow Estate, legal documents, 4 March 1912
  - William G. Winslow Estate, legal documents, 1912
  - William G. Winslow Estate, bonds, 1912-1913
  - William G. Winslow Estate, legal documents, 1913-1914
- (Box Winslow Family, Miscellaneous)
  - William G. Winslow Estate, legal documents, 1915-1916
  - William G. Winslow Estate, legal documents, 22 January 1918
  - William G. Winslow Estate, legal documents, 1922, 1924
  - William G. Winslow Estate, legal documents, 1933-1934
  - William G. Winslow Estate, legal documents, n.d.
  - William G. Winslow Estate, notes, n.d.
  - William Gaston Winslow, correspondence, 1903-1904
  - William Gaston Winslow, quit claim deed, 1911
  - Annie Winslow Chadwick Estate, legal documents, 1924, 1926-1927
  - Deed, Asa & Elizabeth Coltron to Luther Willis, 31 October 1818
  - "Breed's Western Almanac for the Year of Our Lord 1848 Being Bissextile, or Leap Year, and till July 4, the 72nd Year of American Independence," 1848
  - Civil War envelopes, ca. 1861-1865
  - Easter service program, 10 April 1887
  - "New-England Historic Genealogical Society," 1903
  - Postcards, Woodrow Wilson inauguration, 5 March 1917
  - "Proceedings of the Virginia Convention, St. John's Church, March 23, 1775, Richmond, VA," 1927
  - Clippings, 1932, 1946, n.d.
  - "A History of St. James' Episcopal Church, Leesburg, Virginia 1734-1934," 22 May 1935
  - "County of Albemarle Virginia Financial Report July 1, 1943-June 30, 1944," 15 Sep 1944
  - "Ten Years of County Manager Government in Virginia: An Experiment in Local Government," 1 September 1945
  - "A Living Memorial to Patrick Henry," 1945
  - "Patrick Henry: Genius of Liberty," 1945
  - Child's drawing, n.d.
  - Business cards, n.d.
  - Embroidery pattern book, n.d.
  - Poems, author unknown, n.d.
  - Postcards, n.d.
  - Postage stamp, n.d.
  - "Pilgrimage to Historic Lebanon," n.d.
- (Box Photographs and Negatives)
  - Photograph: John Moore Sr. & Mary Chinn Moore, ca. 1890s
  - Photograph: Japanese luncheon (Pauline Winslow, Mary Stedman Williams, Charlotte Becker, Lizzie King, Dixie Ussher, Mary Louise Winslow, Helen Winslow), 1 February 1897
  - Photograph: Pauline Winslow Williams, 1899
  - Photograph: George Brownell, 1911
  - Photograph: Winslow Williams, 1922
  - Photograph: Jonas Harrison home place Shelby County, TX, 1934
  - Photograph: United Distilleries Co. Havana, Cuba, 1937
  - Photograph: Mary Harrison, December 1944
  - Photograph: Enos Ray, 1950
  - Photograph: Leesburg Opera House/Town Hall, 17 December 1954
  - Photographs (5): camping trip at Mary's Rock, 1957
  - Photograph: snow scene, winter 1960
  - Photograph: William G. Winslow, 1978
  - Photograph: alligator in Sanibel Island Florida, 1982
  - Photograph: Chloe Anne Adams, n.d.
  - Photograph: Griffin Stedman Williams, n.d.
  - Photograph: James C. Harrison, n.d.
  - Photograph: James C. Harrison, n.d.
  - Photograph, Mary Harrison Williams, n.d.
  - Photograph: Mary Wilson Pearce, n.d.
  - Photograph: John Moore Sr., n.d.
  - Photograph: J. Miller & Susan Lock, n.d.
  - Photographs (6): unidentified people, n.d.
  - Photographs (4): unidentified outdoor scenes, n.d.
  - Negatives: Constance Williams graduation from Sweet Briar, May 1968
  - Negatives: wedding & Richmond Times Dispatch Marathon, n.d.
  - Negatives: graduation George Mason University, n.d.
  - Negative: Chloe Anne Adams, n.d.
- (Box Photographs, Negatives and Slides)
  - Mary Harrison (Williams), ca. 1862
  - M. Marechal, 3 April 1866
  - Pauline Winslow (Williams), 10 January 1876
  - Mary Clarke Winslow, n.d.
  - Betsey Cooke Harrison, n.d.
  - Griffin Stedman Williams, n.d.
  - Unidentified man, n.d.
  - 3 unidentified girls, n.d.
  - Unidentified woman, n.d.
  - Unidentified woman, n.d.
  - Unidentified woman, n.d.
  - Unidentified woman, n.d.
  - Unidentified woman, n.d.
  - Unidentified woman & girl, 1854
  - Unidentified woman (tinted), 1875
  - James C. Harrison, ca. 1880
  - James C. Harrison (tinted), ca. 1880
  - Jane Abbott Williams & Harrison Williams, Jr., ca. 1904
  - Henry Winslow, September 1908
  - Pauline Winslow Williams & Winslow Williams, 1913
  - Pauline Winslow Williams & Winslow Williams, 1913
  - Winslow Williams, ca. 1913
  - Polly Gardiner, May 1914
  - Winslow Williams, ca. 1916
  - Winslow Williams, ca. 1916
  - Harrison Williams, Jr. & Winslow Williams, ca. 1916
  - Harrison Williams, Jr. & Winslow Williams, ca. 1917
  - Harrison Williams, Jr. & Winslow Williams, ca. 1917
  - Harrison Williams, Jr., ca. 1917
  - Harrison Williams, Jr. (duplicate), ca. 1917
  - Winslow Williams, 1918
  - Harrison Williams, Jr. & Winslow Williams, 1918
  - Winslow Williams, ca. 1918
  - Harrison Williams Jr. & Winslow Williams, ca. 1918
  - Harrison Williams III, 1954
  - Outdoor market with baskets, May 1960
  - Christopher Williams, June 1975
  - Mary Anne Clarke, n.d.
  - Ida Stone Winslow, n.d.
  - Pauline Winslow, n.d.
  - Harrison Williams, n.d.
  - Helen Corbell, Perry Gibson, Betty Welbourne, Janet Harris, Catherine Miller, and John Miller, n.d.
  - Harrison Williams, Harrison Williams Jr., Winslow Williams, and 3 unidentified men, n.d.
  - Harrison Williams, n.d.
  - Winslow Williams, Benjamin Toxford, & Alfred Zerega III hunting, n.d.
  - Tony & Nancy Renler at horse show, n.d.
  - Helen Williams, n.d.
  - Helen Williams on beach, n.d.
  - Helen Williams and child on beach, n.d.
  - Helen Williams and child on beach, n.d.
  - "Harrison and friend," Harrison Williams III and tortoise on beach, n.d.
  - Ben MacIlhaney & Helen Williams, n.d.
  - Helen Williams & unidentified woman, n.d.
  - Smith Bowman, n.d.
  - Aldie Virginia Episcopal Church, n.d.
  - Williamstead, n.d.
  - Williams family group (individuals unidentified), n.d.
  - Williams family with travel home (individuals unidentified), n.d.
  - Unidentified girl, n.d.
  - Unidentified infant, n.d.
  - 2 unidentified girls, n.d.
  - Unidentified woman, n.d.
  - Unidentified boy, n.d.
  - Unidentified boy, n.d.
  - 2 unidentified boys, n.d.
  - 2 unidentified boys, n.d.
  - Unidentified woman & infant, n.d.
  - Unidentified boy, n.d.
  - Dogs playing in yard, n.d.
  - Hog slaughtering, n.d.
  - Fireplace in unidentified house, n.d.
  - House, n.d.
  - Threshing scene, n.d.
  - Honor Roll, Loudoun County, n.d.
  - Dirt road, n.d.
  - Constance Williams & Harrison Williams III, n.d.
  - Constance Williams & Harrison Williams III, n.d.
  - J. Moore Sr. & unidentified woman, n.d.
  - Unidentified house, n.d.
  - Unidentified people, n.d.
  - Unidentified woman & boat, n.d.
  - Unidentified scenes with boat, n.d.
  - Unidentified scenes with boat, n.d.
  - Unidentified scenes with boat, n.d.
  - Unidentified scenes with boat, n.d.
  - Mary Peyton Darling, #384-385, n.d.
  - Janet Harrison, #738, n.d.
  - Janet Harrison, #738-2, n.d.
  - Janet Harrison, #738-3, n.d.
  - Janet Harrison, #738-4, n.d.
  - Janet Harrison, #738-5, n.d.
  - Janet Harrison, #738-7, n.d.
  - Janet Harrison, #738-8, n.d.
  - Janet Harrison, #738-9, n.d.
  - Janet Harrison, #738-10, n.d.
  - Petty Girls, #842, n.d.
  - Petty Girls, #842, n.d.
  - Petty Girls, #842-1, n.d.
  - Petty Girls, #842-2, n.d.
  - Petty Girls, #842-3, n.d.
  - Petty Girls, #842-4, n.d.
  - Petty Girls, #842-5, n.d.
  - Petty Girls, #842-6, n.d.
  - Petty Girls, #842-7, n.d.
  - Petty Girls, #842-8, n.d.
  - Petty Girls, #842-9, n.d.
  - Petty Girls, #842-10, n.d.
  - Petty Girls, #842-12, n.d.
  - Petty Girls, #842-16, n.d.
  - Miss Virginia Lewis house, #832-2 [see enclosure 1043], ca. 1950
  - Miss Virginia Lewis house, #832-1 [see enclosure 1043], ca. 1950
  - Miss Virginia Lewis house, [see enclosure 1043], ca. 1950
  - Miss Virginia Lewis house, [see enclosure 1043], ca. 1950
  - Miss Virginia Lewis house, [see enclosure 1043], ca. 1950
  - Miss Virginia Lewis house, [see enclosure 1043], ca. 1950
  - Family, #1569, 24 Oct 1948
  - Unidentified boy, [see enclosure 2279], n.d.
  - Unidentified building, [see enclosure 2279], n.d.
  - Unidentified man, [see enclosure 2391], n.d.
  - Williams family, #2441, 21 May 1950
  - Williams family, #2441, 21 May 1950
  - Williams family, #2441, 21 May 1950
  - Williams family, #2441, 21 May 1950
  - Williams family, #2441, 21 May 1950
  - Williams family, #2441, 21 May 1950
  - Williams family, #2441, 21 May 1950
  - Williams family, #2441, 21 May 1950
  - Williams family, #2441, 21 May 1950
  - Harrison Williams III, #6263, 7 August 1955
  - Vacation, #6383, n.d.
  - Vacation, #6383, n.d.
  - Constance Williams, #6663, 12 December 1956
  - Constance Williams, #6663, 12 December 1956
  - Christmas door, #6687, 1956
  - 118 envelopes, n.d.
  - Unidentified (2 slides), n.d.
- (Box Photographs)
  - Florida, Hank's Boat, Ned Wedding 1964 (89 photographs), 1964
  - Europe 1969 (84 photographs), 1969
  - St. Maarten, Cockfight 1972 (92 photographs), 1972
  - St. Bart's, St. Maarten 1973 (63 photographs), 1973
  - St. Maarten 1973 (93 photographs), 1973
  - St. Maarten, SABA 1973 (118 photographs), 1973
  - Flowers/Things, Ann Moore, Forney, Visit Crabites 1973 (11 photographs), 1973
- (OMB 2)
  - Williams Family - Oversized documents
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 19 November 1932
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 25 March 1934
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 29 April 1934
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 18 February 1935
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 5 August 1936
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 27 April 1941
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 15 May 1941
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 4 June 1941
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 17 June 1941
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 25 June 1941
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 26 June 1941
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 23 July 1941
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 1 August 1941
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 11 October 1941
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 12 December 1941
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 30 January 1942
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 5 April 1942
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 31 May 1942
    - Harrison Williams, correspondence, 12 January 1944
    - Harrison Williams, Antiques: The Magazine, October 1949
- (OMB 2)
  - Oversized documents
    - Harrison Family: James C. Harrison, receipt, 1865
    - Williams Family: William Williams, account with Robinson Cox & Co., 1870
    - Williams Family: Griffin Stedman Williams, receipt, 9 March 1870
    - Williams Family: Griffin Stedman Williams, appointment as commercial agent for the United States at Nottingham England, 9 September 1885
    - Williams Family: Griffin Stedman Williams, Special Passport, 25 September 1885
    - Williams Family: Mary Harrison Williams Estate, insurance certificates, 5 & 15 May 1911
    - Williams Family: Gordon Williams, passport, 12 February 1917
    - Williams Family: Harrison Williams, stamped envelope, 1943
    - Williams Family: Harrison Williams, Masonic certificate, 7 November 1900
    - Williams Family: Jane Abbott Williams, Infant's Weight Chart for Harrison Williams, Jr., 6 February 1904
    - Williams Family: Pauline Winslow Williams Estate, accounting from the Marine Trust Company of Buffalo, 1932-1933
    - Letter - Marine Committee to John Ashmead (Photostat), 12 July 1776
    - Flower pattern, n.d.
    - Pedigree chart of Nathan Winslow Williams, n.d.
    - Tombstone rubbing, James C. & Mary Harrison Williams grave, n.d.
    - Betsey Cooke Harrison family tree, n.d.
- (OMB 2)
  - Photograph albums
    - Winslow Williams, photograph album and scrapbook, 1920-1950
    - Harrison and Pauline Williams, photograph album - 6 month wedding trip to Europe, 1911
    - Griffin Stedman Williams, photograph album, 1862-1869
    - Winslow Williams, photograph album - family photographs from vacation, n.d.
    - Winslow Williams, photograph album - family photographs, 1913-1930, n.d.
- (OMB 2)
  - Artifacts
    - Artifact Tray 1
      - Daguerreotype: Unidentified woman, n.d.
      - Daguerreotype: Unidentified man, n.d.
      - Daguerreotype: Unidentified woman and child, n.d.
      - Daguerreotype: Unidentified woman, n.d.
    - Artifact Tray 2
      - Stamp moistener, n.d.
      - Eliza Pearce calling card plate, n.d.
    - Artifact Tray 3
      - Griffin Stedman Williams bookplate (metal), n.d.
      - James Harrison calling card plate, n.d.
      - Roxbury Hall address plate, n.d.
      - Initial "H" metal block, n.d.
    - Artifact Tray 4
      - Cards on a string (Chinese/Japanese/Korean writing?), n.d.
    - Artifact Tray 5
      - Mary Harrison Williams calling card plate, n.d.
      - Picture - unidentified child, n.d.
      - Tintype - unidentified girl, n.d.
      - Daguerreotype - unidentified woman (case broken), n.d.
      - Daguerreotype - unidentified man and woman, n.d.
      - Daguerreotype - unidentified man (top of case missing), n.d.
      - Image in daguerreotype case (top of case missing), n.d.
      - Miniature portrait - unidentified woman, n.d.
    - Artifact Tray 6
      - Key, William Winslow Estate papers (see also Order of Publication 17 June 1924), n.d.
    - Artifact Tray 7
      - Cake in decorative box - Harrison and Pauline Williams' wedding, n.d.
    - Artifact Tray 8
      - Book of Common Prayer - Mary Pearce Harrison from Eliza Pearce, 25 November 1856
    - Artifact Tray 9
      - Valentine's Day memento, Harrison Williams to Pauline Williams, n.d.
      - Baggage Passes:
        - Bath & Hammondsport Railroad (7), 1904-1912
        - Buffalo, Rochester & Pittsburgh Railway Company (7), 1899-1908
        - Central Railroad of New Jersey (3), 1909-1912
        - The Delaware, Lackawanna & Western Railroad Co. (6), 1907-1912
        - Erie Railroad Company (20), 1899-1913
        - Tall Brook Route: Pine Creek Railway; Fall Brook Railway; Syracuse, Geneva & Corning Ry; Geneva & Lyons R.R. (1), 1899
        - The Hocking Valley Railway Co. (6), 1903-1908
        - Hudson & Manhattan Railroad Company, Hudson Tunnel System (3), 1910-1912
        - Interborough Rapid Transit Company (5), 1910-1912
        - The Lake Keuka Navigation Company (6), 1905-1912
        - The Lake Shore and Michigan Southern Railway Company (9), 1876-1912
        - Lehigh Valley Railroad (8), 1907-1913
        - New Jersey & New York Railroad Company (3), 1899-1901
        - New Jersey Terminal Railroad Company (1), 1905
        - New York Central and Hudson River Railroad Company (10), 1899-1912
        - New York, Susquehana and Western R.R. (3), 1899-1901
        - Northern Railroad Co. of New Jersey (3), 1899-1901
        - Pennsylvania Railroad Co. (7), 1901-1912
        - Pullman's Palace Car Co./The Pullman Company (13), 1899-1911
        - Western New York & Pennsylvania Railway (2), 1899-1900
      - Baggage Passes:
        - The New York Transfer Co. (3), 1904-1906
      - Shipping Passes:
        - Wells Fargo & Company Express, 1904-1912
      - Telegraph Passes:
        - The Western Union Telegraph Company (12), 1902-1912
        - Wells Fargo & Company Express envelopes (5) 1904-1905, n.d.
    - Artifact Tray 10
      - Wedding slippers, Mary Harrison Williams, 1871
    - Artifact Tray 11
      - Daguerreotype, cased (intact) Ida Stone Winslow, n.d.
      - Daguerreotype, cased (intact) unidentified man, n.d.
      - Photograph (framed) Mary Nash Grandy, n.d.
      - Painting on wood, Pauline Winslow, n.d.
      - Daguerreotype, cased (top detached) unidentified woman, n.d.
      - Daguerreotype, cased (top missing), unidentified girl - tinted, n.d.
      - Tintype - unidentified boy, n.d.
      - Tintype - unidentified boy, n.d.